A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Countries, Series E FA341
Rockefeller Archive Center
- El Salvador
  - El Salvador - General Correspondence, 1948-1971 (Box 30, Folder 236)
    Appeals. Declined. Also copy of NAR notes on trip to El Salvador, 1956 attached memo.
  - El Salvador - Castro, Hector David, 1945-1946 (Box 30, Folder 237)
    El Salvadorian diplomat. Active at United Nations conference. Personal correspondence and letters of congratulations from NAR for role in conference.
  - El Salvador - de Sola, Francisco ("Chico"), 1956-1965 (Box 30, Folder 238)
    Friend of NAR, prominent businessman. Personal and some business related correspondence.
  - El Salvador - Government, 1956, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 239)
    Memo re: NAR 1956 trip to El Salvador. Thanks for official Salvadoran condolences on Robert F. Kennedy's death.
  - El Salvador - Lemus, Jose Maria, Lt. Col., 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 240)
    President, El Salvador, 1957-1960. Overthrown, 1960. Personal correspondence between NAR and President and Mrs. Lemus. NAR letters offering help to Mrs. Lemus on a housing project in which she was active.
- England
  England
  - England - General (A-K), 1947-1971 (Box 30, Folder 241)
  - England - General (L-Z), 1947-1971 (Box 31, Folder 242)
  - England - British Institute for Political Research, 1948-1950 (Box 31, Folder 243)
    Correspondence asking NAR to participate in activities of the Institute. Copies of magazine "European Affairs" published by Institute.
  - England - Catlin, George E. C., Professor - St. Cross College, Oxford Institute of Atlantic Studies, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 244)
    Appeals for Rockefeller Brothers Fund funding of institute to study free trade. Apparently declined. Sent excerpt from study mentioning NAR.
  - England - Children's World Community Chest, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 245)
  - England - Churches, 1955-1966 (Box 31, Folder 246)
    Appeals for funds for historical preservation of churches, declined. Dana Creel, G. Setzer discussed United States fund drive for money for repairs on several churches.
  - England - Eden, John R., Mrs., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 247)
  - England - Foges, W. - Adprint Ltd. & Magazine - "Future", 1947-1948 (Box 31, Folder 248)
    Correspondence re" Foges' method for reproducing maps and his appeal for support. Foges and Lord Glenconner also sent copies of "Future" magazine to NAR.
  - England - Fraser, Arthur Ronald, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 249)
    Affiliated with Royal Institute of International Affairs. NAR gave him letters of introduction in Brazil, Venezuela, Ecuador.
  - England - Gavin, Sir William, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 250)
    Studied Latin American agriculture. Eager to cooperate with NAR in developing Latin American agriculture.
  - England - Government, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 251)
    Condolence letter to the Queen re: Winston Churchill's death.
  - England - Loudon, John H., 1947-1965 (Box 31, Folder 252)
    President, Royal Dutch Shell. Personal correspondence with NAR; correspondence re: Loudon and Royal Dutch Shell interest in South American development through such projects as the Venezuelan Basic Economy Corporation.
  - England - McColl, Sir Alexander, Alastair and RB, 1947-1961 (Box 32, Folder 253)
    Leader in British petroleum industry. NAR introduces son, Alastair, to figures in oil industry in Latin America.
  - England - McNeil, Hector, 1949, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 254)
    British delegate to United Nations. Informal correspondence and clippings re: NcNeil's funeral.
  - England - Straight, Whitney, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 255)
    Seeks NAR or Rockefeller Foundation backing to produce a film based on drawings of da Vinci, which are in Windsor Castle and are property of the Queen. NAR referred the request to the Rockefeller Foundation.
- Finland
  Finland
  - Finland - General, 1948-1963 (Box 32, Folder 256)
    Appeals, declined. NAR letters to President of Finland and Finnish ambassador thanking them for the Order of the White Rose.
- France
  France
  - France - General (B), 1947-1971 (Box 32, Folder 258)
  - France - General (A), 1947-1971 (Box 32, Folder 257)
  - France - General (C), 1947-1971 (Box 32, Folder 259)
  - France - General (D-F), 1947-1971 (Box 32, Folder 260)
  - France - General (G-I), 1947-1971 (Box 32, Folder 261)
  - France - General (J-L), 1947-1971 (Box 33, Folder 262)
  - France - General (M), 1947-1971 (Box 33, Folder 263)
  - France - General (N-P), 1947-1971 (Box 33, Folder 264)
  - France - General (R-V), 1947-1971 (Box 33, Folder 265)
  - France - Speech by French Minister of Foreign Affairs at United Nations General Assembly (Maurice Couve de Murville)., 1947-1971 (Box 33, Folder 265A)
  - France - General (W-Z), 1947-1971 (Box 34, Folder 266)
  - France - Bosworth, Welles, 1939-1966 (Box 34, Folder 267)
    Expatriate American architect, supervised restoration of Rheims Cathedral. Died 1966. Personal correspondence, some of it re: art works. NAR also sought to buy and bring to United States orange trees like those John D. Rockefeller, Jr. bought.
  - France - Churches - Convents, 1956-1971 (Box 34, Folder 268)
  - France - Conseil Artistique des Musees Nationaux (Art Council of the National Museum of France), 1947-1971 (Box 34, Folder 269)
    1947 correspondence between NAR and Council. NAR accepted invitation to become member of the Council, against the advice of members of his staff.
  - France - de Benouville, P., 1948 (Box 34, Folder 270)
    Sends NAR mimeographed material analyzing 1948 elections, which he suggested might be useful to NAR during official visit by Mr. Pierre de Gaulle.
  - France - de Bernaschina, Mario, 1945-1961 (Box 34, Folder 271)
    Works for Porter and Porter, Paris art dealers. Correspondence mostly with Mr. Alfred Barr's office at Museum of Modern Art, offering NAR art works for sale.
  - France - de Gaulle, Charles, General-President, 1960-1970 (Box 34, Folder 272)
    NAR statement on death of de Gaulle, NAR letter to de Gaulle thanking him for interview during 1963 visit; correspondence and memos re: de Gaulle visit to United States in 1960 and NAR's appoitment with him. Photo of NAR and de Gaulle.
  - France - de la Nux, Mrs. Lilie, 1932-1959 (Box 34, Folder 273)
    NAR stayed with family one summer when he was in college. Later helped find her children scholarships and sent her an anonymous gift.
  - France - Hospitals, 1949-1958 (Box 34, Folder 274)
    Appeals. Some referred to Rockefeller Brothers Fund. Declined.
  - France - Marc, Alexandre, 1956-1969 (Box 34, Folder 275)
    Appeals and requests for appointment to see NAR. All declined. Marc has studied federalism and wanted to talk to NAR about his lectures and book on that subject.
  - France - Printed Matter - Information Service - Ambassade de France, undated (Box 34, Folder 276)
  - France - Schools, 1948-1962 (Box 34, Folder 277)
- Germany
  Germany
  - Germany - General (A-H), 1947-1971 (Box 34, Folder 278)
    Appeals. Declined. Letter to Chancellor Erhard from NAR thanking the Chancellor for his hospitality.
  - Germany - General (I-O), 1947-1971 (Box 35, Folder 279)
  - Germany - General (P-Sc), 1947-1971 (Box 35, Folder 280)
  - Germany - General (So-Z), 1947-1971 (Box 35, Folder 281)
  - Germany - Scheiffarth, Engelbert, 1968-1972 (Box 35, Folder 282)
    Met NAR in Bonn in 1963 and gave his family tree. Correspondence included good wishes, genealogical information and requests for genealogical information.
  - Germany - Schools and Colleges, 1955-1964 (Box 35, Folder 283)
- Greece
  Greece
  - Greece - General (A-L), 1947-1971 (Box 35, Folder 284)
    Appeals. Declined. Also a 1947 letter from Mr. Kenneth Iverson of the American Aid Mission in Greece re: guerilla warfare in Greece, outside source of supply, determination of the Greek guerillas and the general weakness of the coalition government and marginal economy.
  - Greece - General (M-Z), 1946-1971 (Box 36, Folder 285)
  - Greece - Chalkias, George and John, 1953-1971 (Box 36, Folder 286)
    Mr. George Chalkias helped NAR in 1953 when their boat caught fire on the coast. Since then, correspondence has consisted of exchanges of good wishes, requests for money (some honored) and requests, declined, from John Chalkias, son, for help from NAR in immigrating to United States.
  - Greece - Greck, S., 1953-1955 (Box 36, Folder 287)
    NAR sent 12 Berlitz books for Greck's classes, which he gave free to the students.
  - Greece - Schools, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 288)
- Guatemala
  Guatemala
  - Guatemala - General Correspondence, 1946-1970 (Box 36, Folder 289)
    Appeals. Declined. Some invitations; some accepted.
  - Guatemala - Churches - Union Church, 1948-1951 (Box 37, Folder 290)
  - Guatemala - Hospitals, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 291)
  - Guatemala - Kyle, Edwin Jackson, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 292)
    1946 report by Dr. Kyle of the American Embassy in Guatemala, on Guatemalan agriculture emphasizing good potential for development and outlining role of United States advisors in the development.
  - Guatemala - Long, Boaz - Restoration of Antigua, 1944-1948 (Box 37, Folder 293)
    Project by Long to restore some historic houses on Antigua. Correspondence and memoranda among NAR and his office and Mrs. Long; re: possible NAR to John Davison Rockefeller, Jr. support proposals by Mr. V. L. Annis for necessary architectural work, and possible purchase by NAR of a house on Antigua. Apparently, Rockefellers did not become involved, though NAR shows some interest.
  - Guatemala - Lope-Herrarte, Mariano, Dr., 1953-1961 (Box 37, Folder 294)
    Minister of Public Health, Guatemala. Personal correspondence between NAR and Lope-Herrarte. Also correspondence re: Rockefeller interest in possible International Basic Economy Corporation role in Guatemalan housing program. Letter from Lope-Herrarte to NAR enumerating elements of growing Communist control in Guatemala.
  - Guatemala - Schools and Colleges, 1955-1956 (Box 37, Folder 295)
    Appeal from University of Guatemala; NAR suggested an appeal to Rockefeller Foundation.
  - Guatemala - Ydigoras Fuentes, Miguel, President, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 296)
    Memo from Berent Friele to NAR re: Friele meeting with President-elect Fuentes. Memo discusses Fuentes' special interest in social programs especially housing. Possible International Basic Economy Corporation role raised. Subsequent general correspondence re: housing program between Fuentes and NAR. Invitation to NAR to inauguration, declined.
- Guyana
  Guyana
  - Guyana, South America - General, 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 297)
    Formerly British Guiana. Appeals. Declined. Congratulations to and informal correspondence with new Prime Minister.
- Haiti
  Haiti
  - Haiti - General (A-F), 1947-1971 (Box 37, Folder 298)
    Appeals and requests for appointment to see NAR.
  - Haiti - General (G-Z), 1947-1971 (Box 37, Folder 299)
  - Haiti - De Catalogne, Gerard, 1946-1954 (Box 38, Folder 300)
    Appeal for NAR contribution for hurricane relief. Contribution sent to Red Cross. Asks NAR for letter of recommendation. Declined.
  - Haiti - Lukens, Glen - Ceramics, 1945-1958 (Box 38, Folder 301)
    Appeals for funds to help support local ceramics industry. NAR contributed.
  - Haiti - Schools, 1952-1956 (Box 38, Folder 302)
- Hawaii
  Hawaii
  - Hawaii - General, 1957-1971 (Box 38, Folder 303)
- Holland
  Netherlands
  - Holland (The Netherlands) - General (A-O), 1949-1970 (Box 38, Folder 304)
  - Holland (The Netherlands) - General (P-Z), 1949-1970 (Box 38, Folder 305)
  - Holland (The Netherlands) - Government, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 306)
    Contribution to Government museum.
  - Holland (The Netherlands) - Jansen-Kaspers, F. R. J. Eibrink, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 307)
    NAR met him during search for Michael when Jansen-Kaspers was in New Guinea as a Dutch government official. Letter to NAR asking NAR's help in obtaining United Nations appointment. NAR and NAR office correspondence with United Nations on Jansen-Kaspers's behalf.
  - Holland (The Netherlands) - Royal Family, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 308)
    NAR's congratulations to Crown Princess Beatrix and husband on their marriage. Clipping and congratulatory telegram on birth of their son.
- Honduras
  Honduras
  - Honduras - General (A-F), 1945-1971 (Box 38, Folder 309)
  - Honduras - General (G-Z), 1945-1971 (Box 39, Folder 310)
  - Honduras - Caceres, Dr. Don Julian R., 1945-1949 (Box 39, Folder 311)
    Honduran Ambassador to the United States was at San Francisco United Nations Conference with NAR. Informal correspondence, including one not re: Honduran position on a question at the United Nations Conference. Also, personal letters of thanks.
  - Honduras - Escuela Agricola Pan Americana, 1951-1959 (Box 39, Folder 312)
    Informal correspondence among NAR, NAR's office, the school director, and people interested in the school. NAR's son Rodman spent a summer there. Copies of school newsletters and annual report, 1953.
  - Honduras - Popenoe, Dr. Wilson, 1948-1957 (Box 39, Folder 313)
    Personal correspondence between NAR and Dr. Popenoe re: Rodman's summer at the school. NAR suggestion that Dr. Popenoe publish some of the school's texts. NAR's letter of testimonial to Dr. Popenoe on Dr. Popenoe's retirement.
- Hong Kong
  Hong Kong
  - Hong Kong - General, 1964-1969 (Box 39, Folder 314)
    Appeals, declined, and greetings.
  - Hong Kong - Montilla, Isabelo J., 1952-1968 (Box 39, Folder 315)
- Hungary
  Hungary
  - Hungary - General, 1954-1971 (Box 39, Folder 316)
- India
  India
  - India - General (A-C), 1954-1971 (Box 39, Folder 317)
  - India - General (D-G), 1954-1971 (Box 39, Folder 318)
  - India - General (H-K), 1954-1971 (Box 40, Folder 319)
  - India - General (L-P), 1954-1971 (Box 40, Folder 320)
  - India - General (R-S), 1954-1971 (Box 40, Folder 321)
  - India - General (T-Z), 1954-1971 (Box 40, Folder 322)
  - India - All-India Handicrafts Board - Mrs. K. Shiva Rao, 1957-1958 (Box 40, Folder 323)
    Correspondence between NAR office and Mrs. Rao re: marketing survey for All-India Handicrafts Board. NAR contributed to defraying the costs of the survey.
  - India - Birla, G. D., 1952-1961 (Box 41, Folder 324)
    Indian businessman and NAR friend. Personal correspondence with NAR. Sends clippings.
  - India - Children's Number of "Shankar's Weekly" - K. Shankar Pillai, Editor, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 325)
    Correspondence among NAR, Museum of Modern Art, and Mr. Pillai re: exchange of ideas concerning children's art. Museum of Modern Art thought highly of "Shankar's Weekly" and Mr. Pillai's international children's art contest.
  - India - da Costa, Eric P. W., 1951-1953 (Box 41, Folder 326)
    Editor of the "Eastern Economist." Sent copies to NAR. Letter of introduction for da Costa to NAR.
  - India - Gandhi, Indira, 1966-1968 (Box 41, Folder 327)
    Became Indian Prime Minister, 1966. Informal correspondence between NAR and Mrs. Gandhi re: Mrs. Gandhi visit to United States, gifts. NAR office memoranda re: gifts, seeing Mrs. Gandhi.
  - India - Government, 1952-1969 (Box 41, Folder 328)
    General government-related memoranda and correspondence re: visit by Minister of Health to United States. Appointment with NAR for foreign secretary. Memo by Tom Keehan of American International Association on impressions of India; report on village development program and Ford Foundation work, agricultural economics, and the political leadership of India which was fragmented and facing great economic problems.
  - India - India Handicraft Project, 1957-1961 (Box 41, Folder 329)
    Project is an offer to increase Indian Handicraft production for export. Correspondence among the Project, NAR office and the Amos Parrish Co. re: marketing report by Parrish on the United States market for Indian crafts. Copy of the report, photos.
  - India - India Handicraft Survey, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 330)
  - India - India Handicraft Reports, 1955-1957 (Box 41, Folder 331)
    Copies of reports on farming and handicrafts.
  - India - Krishaswami, A., 1955-1957 (Box 41, Folder 332)
    Pro-American Indian politician. Met and spoke with NAR re: Indian-United States relations. Correspondence re: meetings; sent NAR copy of report on religious rights and practices he wrote for the United Nations.
  - India - Masuni, M. R., 1951-1963 (Box 41, Folder 333)
    Indian politician, saw and corresponded with NAR. Committed anti-Communist. Informal correspondence including copies of pamphlets from the Democratic Research Service in Bombay sent to NAR.
  - India - Meneses, Anthony G., 1948 (Box 41, Folder 334)
    Indian Trade Commissioner for various Latin American countries. File consists mainly of copies of letters of introduction from Frank Jamieson for Meneses to various people with Latin American connections.
  - India - Pathfinders Association, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 335)
    Created by Commandant General M. J. B. Maneckji to be group of private citizens of Britain, India, and the United States interested in a democratic India. Memo from Stacy May to NAR outlining Association's goal and recommending NAR meet with Maneckji.
  - India - Sarabhai, G. & A., 1946-1949 (Box 41, Folder 336)
    Informal correspondence re: visits with NAR, politics in independent India, Sarabhai interest in housing. NAR asked Wallace Harrison to send a bibliography on housing. NAR asked Chase Bank for credit check on Gautam Sarabhai. Sent NAR a magazine as a gift.
  - India - Schools and Colleges, 1951-1957 (Box 42, Folder 337)
  - India - Sen, Dr. S. C., 1948 (Box 42, Folder 338)
    Interest in program of American medical training for prospective Indian physicians. Left NAR a copy of report he wrote. Correspondence with Rockefeller foundation re: Indian doctor program. Foundation did not give funds.
  - India - Shakeri, Farrukh Sayer, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 339)
    Correspondence and memoranda re: Rockefeller family office not accepting any more mail from Shakeri.
  - India - Printed Matter and Clippings, 1948-1960 (Box 42, Folder 340)
    Includes copy of article by Indian Ambassador Bk. Nehru, copies of Indian government publications, clippings.
- Indochina
  Vietnam
  - Indochina - General, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 341)
- Indonesia
  Indonesia
  - Indonesia - General, 1948-1971 (Box 42, Folder 342)
    Appeals. Declined. Copies of bulletin put out by the Indonesian Information Service.
  - Indonesia - Sastroamidgoro, Dr. Ali, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 343)
    Indonesian Ambassador to the United States. Correspondence and memoranda re: NAR meeting with the Ambassador. Ambassador's standing with the newly-appointed Indonesian prime minister. Copies of Indonesian Information Service Bulletin.
- Iran
  Iran
  - Iran - General, 1948-1969 (Box 42, Folder 344)
    Appeals. Declined. Clippings. NAR letters of thanks and regrets to Iranian offficials.
  - Iran - School and College, 1957-1958 (Box 42, Folder 345)
    Appeals. Declined. Correspondence and memorandum re: plan by Iranian government to set up an American-style university in Shiraz. Memo proposal Ford Foundation contact by Iran; NAR and Foundation interested in plan, that was backed by Iranian government.
  - Iran - Government, 1957-1968 (Box 42, Folder 346)
    Winthrop Rockefeller letter to Shah thanking him for his hospitality in Iran and inviting him to dine with Rockefellers in New York during Shah's visit to United States. Memo to NAR re: possible development of pipe line and plastics factory in Iran. Various letters of thanks to Shah and government officials.
  - Iran - Mehra, Dr. Tobab - Nemazee Hospital - Shiraz Medical Center, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 347)
    Informal correspondence with NAR. Memo on American-style university in Shiraz.
    Related Archival Materials note
    See Iran - Schools and Colleges.
  - Iran - Plan Organization, 1957-1962 (Box 42, Folder 348)
    Correspondence between NAR and Hector Prud'homme re: development in Iran of warehousing program and of chemical-fertilizer plant. Also memos within Rockefeller offices re: these projects, arrest of former Iranian planner.
- Ireland
  Ireland
  - Ireland - General (A-Z), 1952-1970 (Box 43, Folder 349)
    Appeals, declined. Personal correspondence between NAR and Stacy May and Mr. Roger Greene with mention of May's report on Ireland.
  - Ireland - Churches, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 350)
- Israel
  Israel
  - Israel - General (A-O), 1952-1970 (Box 43, Folder 351)
    Appeals. Declined. Clippings. Impersonal correspondence with Herbert Lehman giving statement to be used on 10th anniversary of Israeli independence.
  - Israel - General (P-Z), 1952-1970 (Box 43, Folder 352)
    Appeals. Declined. Clippings.
  - Israel - Ben Gurion, Prime Minister David, 1960-1968 (Box 43, Folder 353)
    Miscellaneous file re: Ben-Gurion visits to New York (1960-1961), gifts to Mrs. Ben-Gurion, clipping of Mrs. Ben-Gurion obituary.
  - Israel - Colleges, 1958, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 354)
    Appeals declined. Correspondence with Hebrew University President re: whom he could contact at Foundation re: grant.
  - Israel - Government, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 355)
    Clipping on Prime Minister Eshkol visit to United States. Memo re: NAR on Prime Minister and Mrs. Eshkol.
  - Israel - The Jerusalem Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 356)
    NAR asked by Mayor of Jerusalem to join. Correspondence with Mayor Kolleck deferring decision on joining; correspondence with Kolleck and Roger Wishnick thanking Wishnick for naming Jerusalem park he donated after NAR. Printed material.
  - Israel - Jerusalem - Hebrew University, 1952-1953 (Box 43, Folder 357)
    Appeal. Declined.
  - Israel - Jerusalem - Nelson A. Rockefeller Park, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 358)
    NAR press release and correspondence expressing gratitude for naming of park. Excerpt from "New York Post" re: dedication of park by David Rockefeller.
- Italy
  Italy
  - Italy - General, 1958-1963 (Box 43, Folder 359)
    Memo re: 1963 dam disaster and possible Rockefeller relief contribution. Printed material.
  - Italy - General Correspondence (A), 1950-1971 (Box 43, Folder 360)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (B), 1950-1971 (Box 44, Folder 361)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (C), 1950-1971 (Box 44, Folder 362)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (D), 1950-1971 (Box 44, Folder 363)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (E), 1950-1971 (Box 44, Folder 364)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (F), 1950-1971 (Box 44, Folder 365)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (G), 1950-1971 (Box 44, Folder 366)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (H), 1950-1971 (Box 44, Folder 367)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (I-K), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (L), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 369)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (M), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 370)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (N), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 371)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (O), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 372)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (P), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 373)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (Q), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 374)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (R), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 375)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (S), 1950-1971 (Box 45, Folder 376)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (T), 1950-1971 (Box 46, Folder 377)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (U), 1950-1971 (Box 46, Folder 378)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (V), 1950-1971 (Box 46, Folder 379)
  - Italy - General Correspondence (W-Z), 1950-1971 (Box 46, Folder 380)
  - Italy - Ambrosiana Library and Gallery, Milan, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 381)
    Correspondence and memoranda among NAR and office staff (chiefly Frank Jamieson) and the library re: possible NAR contribution for the restoration of the library. NAR did not contribute.
  - Italy - Association of Friends of Brera; NAR - Honorary Triennial Member (Florentine Flood Relief), 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 382)